[Music]
[音乐]
this is nick with logosbynic.com and in
我是logosbynic.com的尼克
this tutorial i'll be demonstrating how
在本教程中，我将演示
you can create this decorative border
您可以创建这个装饰性边框
design
设计
using inkscape before we get started
在开始之前使用Inkscape
though if you'd like to learn
不过，如果你想了解
everything that there is to know about
所有要知道的事情
inkscape be sure to check out my
Inkscape一定要查看我的
inkscape master class
Inkscape大师班
it's a collection of over 60 videos
这是60多个视频的集合
where i go over every tool and feature
在那里我检查了每一个工具和功能
in inkscape
在Inkscape
and i explain what it is and demonstrate
我解释了它是什么，并展示了
how it works i'll have a link to that in
它是如何工作的，我会在
the description of the video if you want
视频的描述(如果需要
to check that out
去看看这一点
so to get us started here in inkscape
为了让我们从Inkscape开始
the first thing we have to do is set up
我们要做的第一件事是设置
our documents let's come over here to
我们的文件让我们到这里来
file
文件
and click on document properties and for
，然后单击文档属性和
this tutorial i want to make sure the
本教程我想确保
display units is set to pixels or px
显示单位设置为像素或像素
and i just want to turn off the
我只想关掉
visibility of the page border right here
页面边框在此处的可见性
where it says show page border and then
其中显示页面边框，然后
close out of that
结束了，结束了
and then we want to come up here to
然后我们想来这里
where it says view make sure you have
上面写着查看，确保你有
custom selected
自定义选定项
and then go to zoom and we'll zoom in at
然后转到ZOOM，我们将放大
one to one
一对一
and then we'll open up the fill and
然后我们会打开填充物
stroke menu which is located right here
位于此处的笔划菜单
or you could press
或者你可以按下
ctrl shift and f on the keyboard to open
键盘上的Ctrl Shift和f键打开
that and then we'll open up the align
然后我们就会打开Align
and distribute menu which is right here
并分发就在这里的菜单
or you can press ctrl
或者您可以按Ctrl键
shift and a to open that and they should
Shift和a来打开它，他们应该
be open right here
就在这里开门
and if you notice they opened in these
如果你注意到它们是在这些地方打开的
separate menus over here so what i'm
在这里分开的菜单，所以我是什么
going to do is i'm going to take this
我要做的就是拿着这个
top menu and just click and drag this
顶层菜单，只需点击并拖动
like this until we get the blue
就像这样，直到我们得到蓝色
activation box
激活框
so i can dock that up top and i have
所以我可以把它停靠在上面，我有
this one open so we have them both open
这个是开着的，所以我们两个都打开了
at the same
在同一时间
time like that and then finally we want
像这样的时间，然后我们终于想要
to come up here to where it says enable
才能到达它所说的启用位置
snapping make sure you have that turned
抓拍确保你把它转到
on
在……上面
and the settings we want turned on for
和我们想要打开的设置
this tutorial are this one right here
这本教程就在这里吗？
that says snap nodes pads and handles
上面写着捕捉节点填充和句柄
the next one that says snap to paths
下一个选项显示捕捉到路径
we're going to want to snap
我们会想要抓拍
to cusp nodes and then snap to smooth
尖点节点，然后捕捉到平滑
nodes as well
节点也一样
okay so the first thing we're going to
好的，我们要做的第一件事是
do is uh we're going to create a square
我们要做的是，呃，我们要创建一个正方形
because the way we're going to approach
因为我们要采取的方式
this border design is that we're going
这个边框设计是我们要去
to design the corners of it first
先设计它的边角
because the corners are pretty
因为角落很漂亮
complicated as well
也很复杂
as as soon as we create one corner we
一旦我们创建了一个角落，我们就
should be able to duplicate it and
应该能够复制它，并且
mirror it and use it as a border that
镜像它并将其用作边框
way so
就是这样的
let's grab the squares and rectangles
让我们抓起正方形和长方形
tool over here
工具在这里
and i'm just going to click and drag on
我只需要点击并拖拽
the canvas i'm going to hold ctrl and
我要拿着的画布按Ctrl键和
shift to create a perfectly symmetrical
转变以创建一个完美对称的
square like that
像这样的正方形
i want to make sure that is black i want
我想确定我想要的是黑色的。
to make sure it has sharp corners come
为了确保它有锋利的拐角
up here
在这上面
to where it says this this icon right
到上面写着这个图标的地方
here that says make karn make
这上面写着让卡恩
corner sharp if it's grayed out and you
如果它是灰色的，那么角落就会变得尖锐，而你
can't click on it that means you already
不能点击，这意味着你已经
have sharp corners like i have here if
有像我这里这样的尖角，如果
you use if yours has rounded corners
如果你的牙齿有圆角，你可以使用
just go ahead and click on that to
只需继续并点击该按钮即可
make those make those corners sharp now
做那些让那些角落变得锋利
what i'm going to do is grab the select
我要做的就是抓起精选
tool
工具
and i want to change the size of this to
我想把这个的大小改成
50 pixels by 50 pixels so
50像素乘以50像素
i'm going to come up here between the w
我要在W和W之间来到这里
and the h which is the width and the
H表示宽度和
height
高度
i'm going to turn on this lock icon
我要打开这个锁图标
right here that says when locked change
就在这里，上面写着当零钱被锁定时
both the width and the height by the
的宽度和高度。
same proportions
相同的比例
and i want to change the width of this
我想改变这个的宽度
to 50. so i'll hit 5.0 and press enter
到50岁。因此我将按5.0并按Enter键
and i want to take the opacity of this
我想把它的不透明性
and bring this down roughly in half
并将这一点降低大约一半
now what i want to do is duplicate this
现在我想要做的是复制这个
so let's right click that and go to
让我们右键单击它，然后转到
duplicate
复本
let's make this duplicate copy red and
让我们把这个副本改成红色，然后
let's add
让我们添加
50 pixels to each dimension of this one
这张照片的每个维度都有50个像素
so 50 plus 50 would be 100 so let's
所以50加50等于100，所以让我们
remove that 1 0 0 and press enter
删除该1 0 0并按Enter键
and now i want to lower that beneath the
现在我想把它降低到
original square so i'm going to come up
原来的正方形，所以我要出来
here to where it says
从这里到它所说的地方
lower selection one step or what i like
将选择降低一步或随我喜欢
to do is just press page down
要做的就是按PAGE DOWN
on the keyboard and it'll lower it
在键盘上，它会降低音量
beneath the black square
在黑色的正方形下
and then i want to click and drag over
然后我想点击并拖动到
both of those and just center them up
把这两个都放在中间
on the vertical and horizontal axis like
在垂直轴和水平轴上，如
that
那
and as i mentioned previously you got to
就像我之前提到的，你必须
make sure you have last selected chosen
确保您已选择最后一次选择
from this drop down otherwise
从这个下拉列表中，否则
you may end up with a different result
你可能会得到一个不同的结果
here okay so once we've done that
这里，好的，一旦我们做完了
let's click off of that to deselect
让我们单击该选项以取消选择
everything let's create another copy of
一切，让我们创建另一个副本
this square here so let's click on the
这个方块，让我们点击
red square
红场
let's duplicate that instead of right
让我们复制它而不是正确的
clicking it and going to duplicate
点击它，然后复制
we'll just press ctrl d on the keyboard
我们只需按键盘上的Ctrl d键
and i'll make that copy black and i will
我会把复印件改成黑色，我会
add another 50 pixels to this one so
在这个上再加50个像素，这样
this one would be
这一张应该是
150 like that and then i will lower that
150美元，然后我会把它降下来
to the bottom
降到最低
with this button up here that says lower
这里有一个按钮，上面写着更低
selection to the bottom or we could
选择到最下面，或者我们可以
press the end
按下末端
key on your keyboard let's press end
键盘上的键让我们按End键
there we go
好了，我们走吧
and then i'll center this up as well
然后我也会把这个放在中心
click and drag over all of that to
单击并拖动所有这些内容以
select it
选择它
center it up vertically and horizontally
垂直居中和水平居中
like that
就像这样
click off of it to deselect everything
单击该选项可取消选择所有内容
and now what i want to do is create a
现在我想要做的是创建一个
rectangle coming down here like an arm
长方形像一只胳膊一样从这里下来
coming extending down from the square so
从广场向下延伸，所以
i'm going to zoom in on this a little
我要把这个放大一点
bit so i can see it better to zoom in
有点，这样我可以更清楚地看到它以便放大
i'm just going to hold ctrl and roll up
我只是要按住Ctrl键然后卷起来
the mouse wheel a few times to move the
鼠标滚轮几次以移动
page around like this just press down
像这样翻页只需按下
the mouse wheel and move the mouse
鼠标滚轮并移动鼠标
and let's grab the rectangles and
让我们抓起长方形和
squares tool let's snap to this top left
方块工具让我们捕捉到这个左上角
corner
拐角
click and drag and then snap to this
单击并拖动，然后对齐到此
bottom corner over here like that
底角在这里，就像这样
and then we'll convert that to a path by
然后我们会将其转换为路径
going to path object to path
转到路径对象到路径
and then let's take the select tool
然后让我们使用选择工具
let's take this bottom arrow right here
让我们把这个底部的箭头放在这里
and just bring this down
然后把这个放下来
like that we want to bring that down let
就像这样，我们想把它降下来
me zoom out i'm going to press 1 on the
我缩小了，我要按1键
keyboard to zoom back out to 100
缩小到100的键盘
and once we've done that let's create a
一旦我们做到了这一点，让我们创建一个
duplicate of that by pressing ctrl
通过按Ctrl复制该文件
d and let's hold shift and click on this
让我们按住Shift键并点击这个
little
一点儿
square right here in the mental in the
方块就在这里在精神上
middle and center this up
把这个放在中间和中间
according to the actually no instead of
根据实际的NO而不是
centering it we're going to align the
以它为中心，我们将对齐
left edges so click on the button that
左边缘，所以点击按钮
says align left edges click off of it to
表示将左边缘对齐，然后单击它以
deselect everything
取消选择所有内容
and let's create another copy for up
让我们为UP创建另一个副本
here up top so let's take this copy
在上面，我们拿这个复印件
right here
就在这里
ctrl d to duplicate it rotate this 90
按Ctrl%d复制它旋转此90
degrees like that
像这样的学位
with this button right here that says
这里有一个按钮，上面写着
rotate selection 90 degrees clockwise
将选区顺时针旋转90度
and then hold shift click on the large
然后按住Shift键单击大图
black square in the background there
背景中有黑色方块
we're going to align top edges and
我们要将顶部边缘对齐并
align left edges like that now click off
像这样对齐左边缘，现在单击关闭
of it to
将其发送到
deselect take a copy of this right here
取消选中在此处复制此内容
click on that
点击该按钮
control d hold shift click on the
Ctrl d按住Shift键单击
smaller black square in the middle there
中间的小黑方块
and let's align the top edges again so
让我们再次将顶部边缘对齐，以便
that we end up with this right here now
我们现在在这里结束这一切
we can click off of this to deselect
我们可以单击此选项以取消选择
everything
所有的一切
so what i'm going to do next is i'm
所以我接下来要做的是
going to take this large black square
我要把这个大的黑色正方形
right here i'm going to duplicate that
就在这里，我要重复一遍
by pressing ctrl d
通过按ctrl d键
i want to make this one red and again we
我想把这个染成红色，然后我们再一次
are going to add 50 to 50 pixels to each
将在每个图像上增加50到50个像素
dimension so let's come up here and
所以让我们走到这里来
change this from 150
将此值从150更改为
to 200 and i want to make sure i have
到200，我想确保我有
this centered up above the other the
这个居中位置高于另一个
other squares here so let me move this
其他方块在这里，让我来移动这个
off to the side i'm going to hold shift
到一边去，我要按住班次
click on one of these squares and then
点击其中一个方块，然后
just center it up on the vertical and
把它放在垂直的中心，然后
horizontal axis like that
像这样的水平轴
click off of it to deselect everything
单击该选项可取消选择所有内容
and now what you want to do is take this
现在你要做的就是拿着这个
red square right here
红色方块就在这里
duplicate it by pressing ctrl d hold
通过按CtrldHold复制它
shift click on this rectangle right here
按住Shift键单击此处的矩形
and go to path difference
然后转到路径差
and then we'll do the same thing over
然后我们再做同样的事情
here for this one take this red square
这里是这个，拿着这个红色的正方形
only this time we're not going to
只是这一次我们不打算
duplicate it we're going to take that as
复制它，我们将把它当作
it is
它是
hold shift click on this rectangle right
按住Shift键右键单击此矩形
here path
此处路径
difference and now what we want to do is
现在我们想要做的是
duplicate
复本
this object by pressing ctrl d
通过按ctrl d键创建此对象
and then just bring this one down here
然后把这个拿下来
like that now we'll take this
就像这样，现在我们要拿这个
little leg right here ctrl d to
小腿就在这里ctrl d to
duplicate it bring this one up here like
复制它，把这个拿过来，就像这样
that
那
and now i want to make it so that these
现在我想做的是让这些
two i want to clip off the
两个我想剪掉的
little the two little tails that are
少了两条小尾巴
extending beyond the uh
延伸到这个之外
border there so to do that let me zoom
边框在那里，这样做，让我放大
in i'm going to hold ctrl roll up the
在我要按住Ctrl键的情况下
mouse wheel
鼠标滚轮
grab the edit pads by nodes tool which
抓取按结点编辑焊盘工具，该工具
is the second tool down from the top up
是自上而下的第二个工具
here
这里
click and drag over these two nodes and
在这两个节点上单击并拖动，然后
then hold ctrl and just click and drag
然后按住Ctrl键并单击并拖动
them both straight up like that until
他们两个都是那样直挺挺的直到
they snap onto the edge of that
他们抓住了它的边缘
rectangle we'll do the same thing over
长方形，我们会做同样的事情
here take this click and drag over those
在这里，点击并拖动到这些上
two
二
hold ctrl click and drag until it snaps
按住Ctrl键并单击并拖动，直到它捕捉到为止
over there like that
就像那样在那边
and now we can zoom back out let's go to
现在我们可以缩小了，让我们来看看
the select tool
选择工具
let's click and drag over everything so
让我们点击并拖动所有内容
we have it all selected
我们都选好了
and now we just want to deselect this
现在我们只想取消选择此选项
black square and deselect this red
黑色方块并取消选择此红色
square so to do that i'm going to hold
所以，为了做到这一点，我要拿着
shift
换班
click on that black square to deselect
单击该黑色方块以取消选择
it hold shift again
它再次按住Shift键
click on this red square to deselect
单击此红色方块以取消选择
that and now what we have selected we
现在我们选择了什么，我们
just want to unify it
只是想把它统一起来
so to do that go to path union
因此，要做到这一点，请转到Path Union
and now i want to hold shift click on
现在我想按住Shift键点击
this red square
这个红色的方块
go to path difference
转到路径差异
now if we press one on the keyboard to
现在，如果我们按键盘上的一个键来
zoom back out to 100
缩小到100
we can click and drag over everything
我们可以点击并拖动所有内容
here bring the opacity all the way up
在这里，把不透明带上来
and you could even unify together by
你们甚至可以通过以下方式统一起来
going to path union
前往Path Union
and now we have a corner to use of this
现在我们有一个角落可以利用这一点
decorative border so let's go ahead and
装饰性的边框，让我们继续
create an actual border around something
在某物周围创建实际边框
using this so
所以用这个
i'm just going to scale this down a
我只想把这件事缩小一点
little bit i'm going to hold ctrl and
我要按住Ctrl键，然后
shift and scale this down
对此进行调整和缩小
i'm going to create like a little
我要创造出一个
rectangle on the canvas here so i'm
画布上的长方形，所以我
going to grab the rectangle tool
我要抓取矩形工具
click and drag to create a rectangle
单击并拖动以创建矩形
like this
就像这样
maybe i will make this a different color
也许我会把这个改成不同的颜色
like something like a light green
像是淡绿色的东西
and i want to use this object right here
我想在这里使用这个对象
as a border around this red rectangle so
作为这个红色矩形的边框，所以
let me grab the select tool
让我拿一下选择工具
let me take this corner let me bring
让我走这个角落，让我带上
this over here it's layered beneath
这个在这里，它被层叠在下面
the uh the green rectangle so i'm just
那个呃绿色的长方形所以我只是
going to come over here to where it says
会走到这里，上面写着
raise selection to the top
将选定内容提升到顶部
and i want to place this in the corner
我想把这个放在角落里
up here like that okay now i want to
像这样上去，好的，现在我想
duplicate this
复制这个
ctrl d to duplicate it bring this down
按Ctrl%d复制可按下此键
here let's flip this
来，让我们把这个翻过来
vertically like that put this over here
像这样垂直地把这个放在这里
like that snap that into this
就像这样把它扣进这个
and let's take both of those right there
让我们把这两个都放在那里
right click
右键单击
duplicate now let's flip these
现在复制一份，让我们把这些翻过来
horizontally
水平地
and bring these over here like this
把这些像这样拿到这里来
okay now in order to close these in all
好的，现在为了把这些都合上
we have to do now is let's click off of
我们现在要做的就是让我们点击
that to deselect everything
要取消选择所有内容
let's grab the edit paths by nodes tool
让我们抓取按结点编辑路径工具
let's click on this border right here
让我们点击这里的边框
and i'm going to take these nodes over
我将接管这些节点
here
这里
i'll probably i should probably zoom in
我可能会我可能应该放大
on this so you can see it better
这样你就能看得更清楚了
click and drag over these nodes right
在这些节点上单击并向右拖动
here and then just bring them over
就在这里，然后把它们拿过来
to this object right here like that
到这里的这个物体，就像这样
we'll do the same thing over here take
我们会在这里做同样的事情
these nodes bring them straight up like
这些节点将它们直接带到上面，就像
that
那
hold ctrl so it locks onto the vertical
按住Ctrl键使其锁定在垂直方向上
axis you can either snap it on there
轴，你可以把它扣在那里
like that
就像这样
or you could just hold ctrl and bring
或者，您也可以按住Ctrl键并
them into so that it protrudes into the
这样它就伸进了
other one
另一个
like that and i prefer doing it that way
就像那样，我更喜欢那样做
because if you don't if you snap them
因为如果你不这样做，如果你把它们拍下来
like that you'll notice if you zoom out
就像这样，如果你缩小，你会注意到的
there's a little bit of a disconnect
有一点脱节
between the two probably difficult to
在两者之间可能很难
see it on my screen but
在我的屏幕上看到它，但是
i can see it pretty well okay so let me
我能看得很清楚，好的，让我来
fix that
把它修好
bring that up further and i'll do the
把这个再提出来，我来做
same thing right here i'll take this
就在这里，我要这个。
bring this in over here hold ctrl bring
把这个拿到这里，按住Ctrl键拿来
that to that side
那边的那个
and then the same thing right here take
然后同样的事情就发生在这里
that bring that to that side like that
把它像那样带到那一边
and there you go okay and using that
这就对了，好的，用它
method
方法
you can use that method to apply this
您可以使用该方法来应用
border to
边界到
any rectangle you'd like so i think that
任何你喜欢的矩形，所以我认为
should do it for this tutorial that is
在本教程中应该这样做，即
how you can go about creating this
您可以如何着手创建此
simple
简单
decorative style border using inkscape
使用Inkscape的装饰风格边框
if you have any questions leave a
如果您有任何问题，请在
comment
评论
below and as always thanks for watching
下面并一如既往地感谢您的收看
[Music]
[音乐]